fnno.com 2018-01-04

# Privacy Statement | FINANCIAL NEWS NETWORK ONLINE

Financial News Network Online (FNNO) Web Site Privacy Statement

This document was last updated on December15, 2010

This Privacy Statement describes our current privacy practices with regard to information we collect when you or your computer interact with our Web sites, including [www.fnno.com](http://www.fnno.com/ "www.fnno.com"), [www.comtex.com](http://www.comtex.com/ "www.comtex.com")

Information Collection and Use  
We collect information from our users and their computers when they view our Web sites. We collect both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information. We also collect information from you when you request support or make inquiries about our products or services.

We may ask you to provide us with personally identifiable information at various points while you use our Web sites, such as when you register for a Web site account or when you purchase products or services from us. Examples of the types of personally identifiable information we collect range from your e-mail address to your name, street address, phone or fax number, and credit card information. We use the personally identifiable information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for products and services, to contact you about your account, to complete and support your activities, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to customize the content of our Web sites. We use your e-mail address and other personally identifiable information to send you notifications about your account, the services you currently use, if any, and legal or policy matters. We may use your e-mail address and other personally identifiable information to send you our newsletter or to communicate with you about products and services we believe may be of interest to you.

We also may use some of this information in anonymous or statistical forms, such as aggregating geographic information from user addresses or types of industries in which users work, to better understand our customers. We also may ask you to optionally provide us information about your interests to be used for similar purposes. We will ask your permission before using this type of information in a way that personally identifies you.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

Log Files  
We use the information in our server log files to analyze trends in the usage of our Web sites, to administer and maintain our Web sites, to track a user's path through our Web sites, and to gather broad demographic statistics about our Web sites and the ways in which they are used. Most of the information in these files is not unique to you as an individual, such as the files requested and pages you visit on our Web sites, the Web sites from which you may have been referred to our Web sites, and information about the type of browser you use and its settings. Some of the log files contain IP addresses and other personally identifiable information, which are used to identify user connections and to resolve technical issues related to administration of our Web sites.

Cookies  
A cookie is a small text file stored on a computer that contains information associated with that computer. Our Web sites use cookies for several purposes, such as maintaining your login state, improving the content of our Web sites, providing you with information tailored to your interests, customizing the content of our Web pages, and improving the security of your use of our Web sites. Login cookies are linked to your e-mail address, which is stored with other personally identifiable information.

DoubleClick DART cookie helps marketers learn how well their Internet advertising campaigns or paid search listings perform. Many marketers and Internet websites use DoubleClick’s DART technology to deliver and serve their advertisements or manage their paid search listings. DoubleClick’s DART products set or recognize a unique, persistent cookie when an ad is displayed or a paid listing is selected. The information that the DART cookie helps to give marketers includes the number of unique users their advertisements were displayed to, how many users clicked on their Internet ads or paid listings, and which ads or paid listings they clicked on.

You can instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies from our Web sites. If you do so, however, you will hinder your experience by, for example, viewing some information on our Web sites and logging into forums and message boards, as well as preventing us from displaying content customized to the preferences you have specified. You should, however, be able to access most parts of our sites that are available to the general public.

Transparent GIF files  
In addition to our own cookies, we use pixels, or transparent GIF files, on our sites to help manage our online advertising and email marketing. These GIF files are provided by one or more third-party service providers, based on our specification as to where they are used. The files enable our service providers to recognize a unique cookie in your Web browser, which in turn enables us and our services providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site.

Examples of the ways in which Comtex and our third party service providers use GIF files include:

• Tracking customer response to advertisements, emails and site content  
• Determining your ability to receive HTML-based email messages. This capability helps us or our service providers send you email in a format you can read  
• Knowing how many users open an email and allowing our service providers to compile aggregated statistics about an email campaign for us  
• Allowing us to better target interactive advertising; enhancing customer support and site usability; and providing offers and promotions that we believe would be of interest to you

To conduct these or other activities, we or our service providers sometimes may link personal information you previously have provided us (such as, for example, your name, e-mail address, and the edition of our product that you purchased) to the information the GIF files provide about how you arrive at, navigate through, and leave our sites.

Disclosure of Information  
We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary

• to fulfill your requests for products or services,  
• to protect the security of our software, services, Web sites, and users,  
• to protect ourselves from liability,  
• to respond to legal process or comply with law, or  
• in connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

We share statistical information about users of our web sites with third parties, including our vendors, customers, potential customers, distributors, and third parties that offer products or services for use with the Financial News Network Online Service. We do not link this information to any personally identifiable information.

We occasionally contract with other companies to provide limited services to us or on our behalf, such as billing or customer support services. When we do so, we provide these companies with only limited access to personally identifiable information.

In addition, we may occasionally join with other reputable companies to provide users with third party products and services. We will notify you at the time that you sign up for these products or services that these third parties will obtain personally identifiable information to provide the requested products or services. This Privacy Statement does not cover these companies' use of the information.

Security  
The Financial News Network Online Service uses encryption technology to protect your privacy and the security of your data and communications. 

Security Measures Related to Your Information  
We take measures to protect the security of personally identifiable information we hold about you. These measures include

• encrypting sensitive information during transmission,  
• limiting the number of our employees who have access to personally identifiable information,  
• requiring employees with access to personally identifiable information to take appropriate measures to safeguard it, and  
• storing your information in secure places that are protected using standard security technologies.  
• segregating payment or account billing information, information collected through customer support, and CSM and other performance and reliability data, and maintaining these types of information separately.

Changes to this Privacy Statement  
Comtex will occasionally update this Privacy Statement as our business and products evolve. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the Privacy Statement. For material changes to this Privacy Statement, Comtex will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.

Contact Us  
If you have questions about this Privacy Statement, its implementation, or our practices, please contact Contract Compliance at [contracts@comtex.com](mailto:contracts@comtex.com).
